（至今走过的路）
爸爸失踪了 我需要你来帮我找到他 我一个人没法做
Dad's missing. I need you to help me. I can't do this alone.
爸爸让我们干这份工作 他希望我们继续
Dad's given us a job to do. He wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
Saving people, hunting things.
那个恶魔杀死了妈妈和杰西
This demon killed Mom and Jess.
我要找到爸爸和杀死杰西的凶手
I gotta find Dad. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
- 我叫梅格 - 你这是去哪？
I'm Meg. - So where you headed?
我绝不会告诉你 因为你可能是个变态
No way l'm telling you. You could be some kind of freak.
爸爸
Dad.
1835年 塞缪尔·柯尔特制造了一把特殊的手枪
In 1835, Samuel Colt made a special gun.
据说这把枪能杀死所有东西
They say this gun can kill anything.
我会在恶梦里看到幻象 而有时那些幻象会成真
l have these nightmares. And sometimes they come true.
你们两个是我唯一拥有的
You two are all I've got…
但我猜我们三个在一起的确会更强大
but I guess we are stronger as a family.
所以猎杀那个恶魔的事情 我们一起去做
We go after this damn thing. Together.
是的 父亲
Yes, sir.
（蓝色的地球 明尼苏达）
早上好 能为您效劳吗？
Good morning. Can I help you?
我想 我有点事… 需要忏悔
I kind of-I need to talk.
那正是我作为牧师的职责
Well, that's what I'm here for.
我做了些事…
I've done some things.
都不是什么好事
Not good things.
没关系 对那些真心忏悔的人而言 宽恕永在
Well, there's always forgiveness for us if we seek it.
对每个人都是吗？你确定？
For everyone? Are you sure?
我想说 救赎正是为罪人而存在的
I like to say: Salvation was created for sinners.
告诉我 是什么事让你耿耿于怀？
Tell me what's on your mind.
我说了谎 很多次
Well, l-I've lied a lot.
我曾偷盗
I've stolen.
我欲望横生
I've lusted.
不久前 我遇见一个男人 他是个好人
And the other day, I met this man. A nice guy, you know?
我们愉快地聊了会儿天 跟现在差不多
And we had a really good chat. Sort of like this.
然后我撕裂了他的喉咙 把他的心脏从胸腔里掏出来
Then I slit his throat and ripped his heart out through his chest.
我是不是一个坏人呢？
Does that make me a bad person?
我知道你是什么东西
I know what you are.
你不可能进来这里的
You can't be here.
这是神的领地
This is hallowed ground.
算了吧 也许这能挡住那些小鬼怪
Please. Maybe that works in the minor leagues…
但对我可行不通
but not with me.
你的力气怎么跟个女人一样
You throw like a girl.
你想要什么
What do you want?
温彻斯特一家
The Winchesters.
我已经有一年多没和约翰·温彻斯特联络了
I haven't spoken to John in over a year.
你是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
即使我知道他们在哪 也绝不会告诉你
Even if I did know where they were, I'd never tell you.
这点我早知道了
I know.
《邪恶力量》
（曼宁 科罗拉多）
就是这样了 这就是我所了解的一切
So this is it. This is everything I know.
我一生都在找这个恶魔
Look, our whole lives we've been searching for this demon, right?
但一直没有线索 一点都没有
Not a trace, just nothing.
直到一年多前 我终于发现了这个恶魔的踪迹
Until about a year ago. For the first time, I picked up a trail.
那正是你离开的时候 没错
- That's when you took off. - Yeah. That's right.
那个恶魔为了进行蛰居必须出来寻找猎物
The demon must have come out of hiding or hibernation.
那么你发现了什么？
So, what's this trail you found?
先是在亚利桑那 然后是新泽西和加利福尼亚
Starts in Arizona, then New Jersey, California.
屋子被焚为平地
Houses burned down to the ground.
发生不幸的总是某个家庭 就像我们家
It's going after families, just like it went after us.
- 有婴儿的家庭？- 对
- Families with infants? - Yeah.
在那个婴儿满6个月的夜晚
The night of the kid's 6-month birthday.
- 我那天是6个月大？- 正好满6个月
- I was 6 months old that night? - Exactly 6 months.
那么 正确地说 那个恶魔是冲着那些婴儿来的
So basically, this demon is going after these kids.
为了某些目的
for some reason.
这么说它也盯上了我
The same way it came for me?
所以妈妈和杰西卡
So Mom's death…
都是因我而死的？
Jess, it's because of me?
- 我们还不能确定 萨姆 - 是吗？
- We don't know that.Sam. - Really?
- 但我却十分确定 - 我已经说过很多次了
- l'd say we're sure. - For the last time…
- 发生这些事不是你的错 - 没错
- …what happened is not your fault. - Right.
- 不是我的错 - 但却是我的问题
- It's not my fault, but it's my problem.
不 那不是你的问题 是我们的问题
No, it's not, it's our problem.
好了 够了
Okay. That's enough.
它为什么要这么做？它想要什么？
So why is it doing it? What does it want?
听着 我也希望我知道答案 真的
Look, I wish I had more answers. I do.
但我总是迟到一步
I've always been one step behind it.
所以没能有时间救下那些家庭
Look, l've never gotten there in time to save…
那么在它再次行动前 我们怎么找到它？
So how do we find it before it hits again?
会有一些征兆
There are signs.
我花了不少时间来总结这些模式
It took me a while to see the pattern…
在火灾的前几天 周围地区会有一系列不寻常的现象
but in the days before these fires, signs crop up in an area.
比如牲口死亡 气温波动
Cattle deaths, temperature fluctuations…
电磁风暴
electrical storms.
我后来回去查过
And then I went back and checked, and…
那些事也曾发生在劳伦斯
These things happened in Lawrence.
就在你母亲死的前一周
A week before your mother died.
同样也发生在帕罗奥图（萨姆就读的斯坦福所在地区）
And in Palo Alto…
在杰西卡死前
before Jessica.
这些征兆现在又出现了
And these signs, they're starting again.
- 在哪？- 爱荷华州的救世郡
- Where? - Salvation, lowa.
什么事？
- Goddamn it. - What is it?
- 混蛋 - 发生什么了？
- Son of a bitch. - What is it?
- 我刚接到迦勒的电话 - 他没事吧？
- I just got a call from Caleb. - ls he okay?
他很好 吉姆·墨菲死了
He's fine. Jim Murphy's dead.
吉姆 那个牧师？
Pastor Jim?
- 怎么会？- 喉咙被割断了
- How? - Throat was slashed.
死于出血过多
He bled out.
迦勒说在吉姆那里发现了硫磺的痕迹
Caleb said they found traces of sulfur at Jim's place.
一个恶魔
A demon.
- 是我们在找的这个 - 我不知道
- The demon? - I don't know.
可能他只是不幸被杀
Could be he just got-He got careless, he slipped up.
也可能是那个恶魔知道我们接近真相了
Maybe the demon knows we're getting close.
- 我们现在怎么做？- 我们现在必须分秒必争了
- What do you wanna do? - Now we act like every second counts.
这个郡有两个医疗中心
There's two hospitals and a health center in this county.
我们分头去找 这样机会大些
We split up, we cover more ground.
我需要出生记录 以及所有在
I want records. I want a list of every infant…
下周满6个月大的婴儿名单
that's gonna be 6 months old in the next week.
爸爸 那样的婴儿有很多 我们怎么知道究竟会是哪个？
That could be dozens of kids. How the hell are we gonna know…
- 我们一个一个查 - 我们会看看 这就是
- …which one's the right one? - We'll check them all, that's how.
你有更好的办法吗？
You got any better ideas?
没有
No, sir.
爸爸
Dad?
什么
Yeah?
那是吉姆
It's Jim.
我不能…
You know, I can't…
我要结束这一切 一定要结束
This ends now. I'm ending it.
无论用什么方法
I don't care what it takes.
资料在这里
Here you go, officer.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
（爱荷华州出生证明）
嗨 需要我为你效劳吗？
Hi. ls there anything I can do for you?
哦 天 当然需要
Oh, God, yes.
实际上 我
Only I…
正在工作 所以…
Working right now, so…
火车
A train.
嗨
Hi.
让我来吧 看来你的手不够用了
Hi. Here, let me hold that. You look like you don't need that anymore.
谢谢
Thanks.
她真漂亮 是你的孩子？
She's gorgeous. Is she yours?
- 是啊 - 嗨
- Yeah. - Hi.
不好意思 我是萨姆 我刚搬过来住
I'm sorry, I'm rude. l'm Sam. I just moved in up the block.
- 哦 嗨 我叫摩妮卡 - 摩妮卡
- Oh, hey. l'm Monica. - Monica.
- 这是罗茜 - 罗茜？
- This is Rosie. - Rosie?
- 嗨 罗茜 - 欢迎入住
- Hi, Rosie. - So welcome to the neighborhood.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 她真乖 - 是啊 她从来不哭
- She's such a good baby. - I know, she-l mean, she never cries.
只是盯着人看
She just stares at everybody.
有时你甚至会觉得
Sometimes she looks at you and I swear it's-
她在读你的思想
It's like she's reading your mind.
那么你呢莫妮卡 你们在这里住了多久？
What about you? Have you lived here long?
我和我丈夫在罗茜出生前买了那边的房子
My husband and l, we bought our place just before Rosie was born.
- 那么罗茜现在多大了？- 她今天正好6个月大
- How old is Rosie? - She's 6 months today.
- 很棒吧 茁壮成长 - 是啊
- She's big, right? Growing like a weed. - Yeah.
- 莫妮卡 - 什么？
- Monica? - Yeah?
万事小心
Just… Just take care of yourself, okay?
你也一样 萨姆 回见
Yeah. You too, Sam. We'll see you around.
- 哦 当然 - 好
- Yeah, definitely. - Okay.
那是爸爸
Oh, there's Daddy.
你在干…
What are you?
罗茜
Rosie.
- 幻象 - 没错
- A vision? - Yes.
我看到那个恶魔把一个女人定在天花板上烧
I saw the demon burning a woman on the ceiling.
你认为这会发生在这个女人身上因为…
You think it will happen to this woman because…?
因为事情总是完全按我看到的发生
Because these things happen exactly the way I see them.
一开始他只是做恶梦
Yeah, they started out as nightmares.
后来连白天醒着也能看到幻象了
Then they started happening while he was awake.
- 没错 要我说 - 我不知道
Yeah. It's like-I don't know.
越接近与那个恶魔有关的事
It's like the closer I get to anything involving the demon…
这些幻象也越清晰
the stronger the visions get.
你们打算什么时候告诉我这些
All right, when were you gonna tell me about this?
我们不知道这意味着什么
We didn't know what it meant.
你弟弟有这种现象
Something like this starts happening to your brother…
你该拿起电话打给我
you pick up the phone and you call me.
给你电话？
Call you?
不是开玩笑吧 爸爸
Are you kidding me?
我在劳伦斯时给你打过
Dad, I called you from Lawrence. All right?
萨姆在我快死的时候也给你打过
Sam called you when I was dying. I mean, getting you on the phone?
接通你电话的几率比我中彩票还低
I got a better chance of winning the lottery.
你说的对
You're right.
虽然我还不太适应你们这种新态度
Although I'm not real crazy…
但你是对的 我很抱歉
about this new tone of yours, you're right. l'm sorry.
听着 不管我看到没看到 事实是
Look, guys, visions or no visions, the fact is…
这个恶魔今晚就会出现
we know the demon is coming tonight.
那家人会像我们一样经历一切
And this family's gonna go through the same hell we went through.
不 他们不会的
No, they're not.
今后也不会再有了
No one is, ever again.
喂 Sam
Hello. Sam?
- 是谁？- 好好想想 你会想起来的
- Who is this? - Think real hard. It'll come to you.
梅格
Meg.
我记得你已经掉出窗外了
Last time I saw you, you fell out of a window.
没错 你们干的好事
Oh, yeah, thanks to you.
顺便说一句 那可着实伤了我感情 伤感情？
- That really hurt my feelings, by the way. Just your feelings?
那不过是逢场作戏罢了
That was a seven-story drop.
让我和你爸爸说话
Let me speak to your dad.
我爸爸 我不知道他在哪里
My dad? I don't know where my dad is.
该是成年人谈正经事的时候了 萨姆 让我和他说话
It's time for the grownups to talk, Sam. Let me speak to him now.
我是约翰
This is John.
嗨 约翰 我是梅格
Howdy, John. I'm Meg.
我是你儿子的一个朋友
I'm a friend of your boys.
也是眼看着你的好朋友吉姆·墨菲淹死在自己血里的人
I'm also the one who watched Jim Murphy choke on his own blood.
还在听吗？约翰
Still there, John boy?
- 我在 - 那是昨天的事
- l'm here. - Well, that was yesterday.
今天我在林肯
Today, l'm in Lincoln…
这里有你的另一个老朋友
visiting another old friend of yours.
他想和你打个招呼
He wants to say hi.
约翰 不管他们做什么 不要给他们…
John, whatever they do, don't give-
迦勒？
Caleb?
迦勒
Caleb.
听着 他没有参与任何事
You listen to me. He's got nothing to do with anything.
放了他
You let him go.
我们知道你得到了柯尔特 约翰
We know you have the Colt, John.
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 噢 好吧
- I don't know what you're talking about. - Oh, okay.
哦 好吧 那听听这个
So listen to this.
迦勒
Caleb.
- 迦勒 - 听到了吗？
- Caleb. - You hear that?
那是你朋友死亡的声音 我们再来一次
That's the sound of your friend dying. Now let's try this again.
我们知道你有那把枪 约翰
We know you have the gun, John. Word travels fast.
对我们而言 你刚刚是在向我们宣战
So as far as we're concerned, you just declared war.
所以那是战争的必备要素 伤亡
And this is what war looks like. It has casualties.
我会杀了你的 你知道
I'm gonna kill you. You know that?
哦 来吧 小心自己的血压
Oh, John, please. Mind your blood pressure.
现实就是这样 我们得继续我们要做的事
So this is the thing: We're gonna keep doing what we're doing.
而你的朋友 任何帮助过你的人
And your friends, anyone who's ever helped you…
那些曾为你提供避难所的人 你爱的人
gave you shelter, anyone you ever loved…
都会死 除非你给我们那把枪
they'll all die unless you give us that gun.
我等着呢 约翰 你最好在下次铃声响起前给我答复
I'm waiting, Johnny. Better answer before the buzzer.
- 我答应你 - 你说什么？我没听太清楚
- Okay. - Sorry, I didn't quite get that.
我说好的 我会给你柯尔特
I said, okay. I'll bring you the Colt.
林肯这有个仓库 就在沃巴什湖街的拐角
There's a warehouse in Lincoln on the corner of Wabash and Lake.
我们在那里见面
You're gonna meet me there.
我需要几天才能开车赶过去
It's gonna take me about a day's drive to get there.
- 今晚午夜在那里见面 - 不可能
- Meet me there at midnight tonight. - That's impossible.
我赶不过去 我不能带把枪直接上飞机
I can't get there in time and I can't just carry a gun on a plane.
哦 那我猜你的朋友就要死了
Oh, then I guess your friends die, don't they?
如果你决定要来赴约的话 一个人来
If you do decide to make it, come alone.
你这是在看什么呢？
What the hell are you looking at?
- 这么说 - 你觉得梅格是个恶魔？
- So you think Meg is a demon?
即使她不是 也肯定被一个恶魔控制着
Either that, or she's possessed by one.
- 无论如何 这并不重要 - 我们现在怎么做？
- lt doesn't really matter. - What do we do?
- 我要去林肯 - 什么？
- l'm going to Lincoln. - What?
我似乎没有选择的余地
Doesn't seem like I have a choice.
如果我不去 很多人会死 我们的朋友会死
If I don't go, a lot of people die. Our friends die.
爸爸 那个恶魔今晚就会出现
Dad, the demon is coming tonight.
袭击莫妮卡和她的家人 我们只有那把枪
for Monica and her family.That gun is all we got.
你不能就这样把枪交出去
You can't just hand it over.
谁说我要交出去
Who said anything about handing it over?
除了我们和那几个吸血鬼
Besides us and a couple vampires, no one's really seen the gun.
- 没人见过这把枪 - 所以没人知道这枪是什么样子
- No one knows what it looks like. - So, what, you're just gonna…
- 那你想怎么样？随便找把枪冒名顶替？- 古董店
- …pick up a ringer at a pawnshop? - Antique store.
你想给梅格一把假枪 指望她不会发现？
You hand Meg a fake gun and hope she doesn't notice?
只要看上去差不多 她应该不会那么快发现
Look, as long as it's close, she shouldn't be able to tell the difference.
但那能拖多久？如果她发现了你怎么办？
For how long? What happens when she figures it out?
我只是想拖延几小时 仅此而已
I just-l just need to buy a few hours, that's all.
你是说给我和迪恩留出几小时
You mean, for Dean and me.
你想让我们留在这里
You want us to stay here…
单独对付那个恶魔
and kill this demon by ourselves?
听着 萨姆
No, Sam.
我不想再失去我爱的人了
I wanna stop losing people we love.
我希望你能去上学 我希望迪恩能有个家
I want you to go to school. I want-l want Dean to have a home.
我希望玛丽活着
I want Mary alive.
我只是…
I just.
只是想要这一切都结束
I just want this to be over.
找到了？
Did you get it?
你知道这是个陷阱 是吧？
You know this is a trap, don't you?
我是说梅格要你一个去
That's why Meg wants you to come alone.
我能对付她 武器我都备全了
I can handle her. I got a whole arsenal loaded.
- 圣水… 护身符 - 爸爸
- Holy water, Mandaic amulets… - Dad…
什么？
What?
- 向我保证 - 保证什么？
- Promise me something. - What's that?
一旦有什么不对 马上跑
This thing goes south, just get the hell out.
千万不要死 你知道你对我们有多重要
Don't get yourself killed, all right? You're no good to us dead.
你们也是
Same goes for you.
听着
All right, listen to me.
这把枪的子弹是特制的
They made the bullets special for this Colt.
现在只剩4发了 没有子弹 这把枪就废了
There's only four of them left, and without them this gun is useless.
- 所以好好用每一发子弹 - 知道了
- You make every shot count. - Yes, sir.
这场仗我们等了很长时间了
I've been waiting a long time for this fight.
可惜我不能参与其中
Now it's here, and l'm not gonna be in it.
你们都长大了
It's up to you boys now.
这是你们的战斗 要你们来打
It's your fight. You finish this.
去终结这场最初由我开始的战斗 明白吗？
You finish what I started. You understand?
我们很快会再见的 爸爸
We'll see you soon, Dad.
再见
I'll see you later.
Later.
要不我们说有煤气泄漏
Maybe we could tell them there's a gas leak.
也许他们会离开家几小时
Might get them out of the house for a few hours.
这种好事有几次发生在我们身上？
Yeah, and how many times has that actually worked for us?
是啊
Yeah.
或者干脆告诉他们真相
We could always tell them the truth.
- 不行 - 我也知道不行
- No. - No, I know, I know.
我只是
I know. I know. I just…
在想该怎么救这些人 Sam 我们一起行动
- With what's coming for these people… - We only got one move and you know it.
等那个恶魔现出真身
We gotta wait for that demon to show itself and then…
然后在它行凶前结果了它
we get it before it gets them.
不知道爸爸现在干得怎么样了
I wonder how Dad is doing.
我希望我们是在那里支援他
I'd feel a lot better if we were there backing him up.
我更希望他能在这里支援我们
I'd feel a lot better if he were here backing us up.
感觉很奇怪
This is weird.
怎么了？
What?
这么多年 我们一直期待着这一刻
After all these years, we're finally here.
现在终于等到了 却有种不真实的感觉
Doesn't seem real.
我们只要尽力做好工作 保住小命 像往常一样
We just gotta keep our heads and do our job, like always.
是啊 但这次不同寻常
Yeah, but this isn't like always.
我承认
True.
迪恩…
Dean…
我想谢谢你
I wanna thank you.
为了什么？
For what?
所有的事情
For everything.
你总是在背后支持我
You've always had my back, you know?
即使我无法依靠其他任何人 我总是能指望和依靠你
Even when I couldn't count on anyone, I could always count on you.
现在…
And now…
这些话我想让你知道
I don't know, I just wanted to let you know.
- 以防万一… - 哇 你开什么玩笑
- Just in case. - Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Are you kidding me?
- 什么？- 不要说什么万一你有什么不测之类的鬼话
- What? - Don't say, "Just in case…
我可还不想听临终遗言
something happens to you." I don't wanna hear that freaking speech, man.
听着 今晚没人会死
Nobody's dying tonight.
我们不会 那家人也不会 没有人
Not us, not that family, nobody.
除了那个恶魔
Except that demon.
那个该死的混蛋活不过今晚
That evil son of a bitch isn't getting any older than tonight.
听懂了吗？
You understand me?
约翰 你来了？
John. You made it.
真是太遗憾了
Too bad, really.
我还想多杀几个人呢
I was hoping to kill more of your friends.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
难怪你两个儿子都长得一表人才
I can see where your boys get their good looks.
不过我得承认
Though I must admit…
我原以为 他们口中的你… 会更高大些
considering what they say about you, I thought you'd be taller.
看来你不太健谈啊…
Well, aren't you the chatty one.
你想直接进入正题吗
You wanna get to business?
也好
Fine.
把枪交出来吧
Why don't you hand over the gun.
如果我这么做了 我怎么活着出去？
If I give you the gun, how do I get out of here?
如果你真如你儿子说的那么棒 你早该想好了
If you're as good as they say you are, I'm sure you'll figure something out.
- 是啊 也许我直接杀你 - 你想杀我吗？请便
- Maybe l'll just shoot you. - You wanna shoot me, baby?
但什么也不会改变
Go ahead. lt won't end anything.
今天来的可不止我一个
There's more where I came from.
那是什么？
Who the hell's that?
他绝对不像我那么有趣 我保证
He's not nearly as much fun as I am, I can tell you that.
所以我建议你交出手枪
So I suggest you give us the gun.
马上
Now.
这是柯尔特？
This is the Colt?
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
你杀我？
You shot me!
我不敢相信你竟然杀了我
I can't believe you just shot me!
这是赝品
It's a fake.
- 你死定了 约翰 你的儿子也死定了 - 我从没用过那枪
- You're dead, John. Your boys are dead. - l've never used the gun.
- 怎么会知道它不管用 - 我现在一点没心情谈这事
- How could I know it wouldn't work? - l'm so not in the mood for this.
我刚被枪杀了
I've just been shot.
那你真该庆幸这枪不是真的
Well, then I guess you're lucky the gun wasn't real.
真有趣 约翰
That's funny, John.
我们要把你的皮剥下来 那一定很有趣
We're gonna strip the skin from your bones, but that was funny.
是圣水 干得不错 约翰
Holy water, John.
真的很可爱
Real cute.
爸爸不接电话
Dad's not answering.
也许梅格迟到了
Maybe Meg was late.
- 也许服务信号不好 - 也许吧
- Maybe cell reception's bad. - Yeah, well…
迪恩 等等
Dean, wait.
听
Listen.
来了
It's coming.
该死
Damn it.
离开我家
Get out of my house!
- 离开我家 - 别动 别动
- Get out of my house! - Please. Please.
- 安静 - 听我说
- Please. - Be quiet and listen to me.
我们是来帮你的 行吗
Be quiet and listen. We are trying to help you.
- 查理 - 有什么事吗？
Charlie. - Okay?
- 一切都好 - 莫妮卡 快去保护孩子
Everything okay down there? - Monica, get the baby!
- 不要去幼儿园 - 你不要接近她
- Don't go in the nursery! - You stay away from her!
你在干。-。-
What are you-?
罗茜
Rosie!
- 它去哪了？- 我的孩子
- Where the hell did he go? - My baby!
- 不 等等 - 你们快离开这里 孩子我来抱
- No. Wait. - Get her out of here. I got it.
- 来吧 - 罗茜
- Take her and go. - Rosie!
- 快走 - 我的孩子…
- Come on. My baby!
迪恩会救出她的
Dean's got her.
- 你们离我家人远点 - 不 查理 他们救了我们
- You get away from my family. - No, Charlie, don't. They saved us.
他们救了我们
I mean, they saved us.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 它还在里面 - 萨姆 萨姆 不
- It's still in there. - Sam. Sam, no.
- 迪恩 让我去 它还在里面 - 你进去就是自杀
- Dean, let me go. It's still in there. - It's suicide.
- 我不在乎 - 我在乎
- I don't care. - I do.
快接电话啊 爸爸 该死
Come on, Dad. Answer your phone, damn it.
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
你听到我说了吗？肯定有事发生了
You hear me? Something's happened.
如果你当时让我进去…
lf you had just let me go in there…
我就能结束这一切
l could have ended all this.
萨姆 你一直这样想会让自己痛苦不堪的
Sam, the only thing you were gonna end was your life.
你不会吗？
You don't know that.
那么 你愿意就这么牺牲自己咯
So, what, you're just willing to sacrifice yourself, is that it?
- 是的 我就是这么想的 - 那不可能 只要有我在一天
- Yeah. Yeah, you're damn right I am. - Well, that's not gonna happen.
- 就不会让这种事发生 - 你在说什么？迪恩
- Not long as I'm around. - What are you talking about, Dean?
我们一生都在追逐这个恶魔
We've been searching for this demon our whole lives.
那是我们唯一在乎的事
It's the only thing we've ever cared about.
萨姆 我也想它死 非常想 但这不值得用你的生命做代价
Sam, I wanna waste it. I do. Okay? But it's not worth dying over.
- 什么 我说真的
- What? - I mean it.
如果猎杀这个恶魔意味着牺牲你
If hunting this demon means you getting yourself killed…
那我但愿我们永远不要找到它
l hope we never find the damn thing.
那东西杀死了杰西
That thing killed Jess.
杀死了妈妈
That thing killed Mom.
你自己也说过的
You said yourself once…
无论我们做什么
that no matter what we do, they're gone.
她们都已经走了 不会再回来了
And they're never coming back.
不许你这么说
Don't you say that. Not you.
经历了那么多事 我不许你再这么说
Not after all this. Don't you say that.
萨姆 听着
Sam, look…
我们三个人
the three of us…
是我们所拥有的一切
that's all we have.
也是我的一切
And it's all I have.
有时我觉得要让我们大家在一起真的很难
Sometimes I feel like I'm barely holding it together, man.
如果失去你或者爸爸…
And without you or Dad.
爸爸
Dad.
他现在该回来了 再打给他试试
He should've called by now. Try him again.
你们俩这次可真把事给搞砸了
You boys really screwed up this time.
他在哪？
Where is he?
你们永远也见不到你们父亲了
You're never gonna see your father again.